A Guide to the Papers of Grace King, 1887-1915
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of Grace King 1887-1915
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
7824
9 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection was deposited by Clifton Waller Barrett on December 17, 1963, accessioned on January 29, 1965, and changed to a gift on July 1, 1991.
Scope and Content
This collection consists of 9 items, chiefly manuscripts and correspondence of Grace King.
Arrangement
This collection consists of two series. Series I includes manuscripts, and Series II includes correspondence.
Contents List
- Series I: Manuscripts
  - "Occasions of adversity ..." 1896 Feb 5, AMsS, 1p. quote.
  - "Every heart ..." 1915 Aug 28, AMsS, 1p. quote.
- Series II: Correspondence
  - Grace King to Mr. W. Smith 1887 Dec 11, ALS, 2p.
    Acknowledges receipt of book from Mr. Smith and replies that she has no printed book to return the favor.
  - Grace King to Mr. Thomas Mason 1888 May 7, ALS, 2p.
    Sends signed note and thanks Mr. Mason for his compliments; w/print of King from Harper's Monthly.
  - Grace King to Mrs. Nixon 1898, Christmas, ALS, 4p.
    Thanks Mrs. Nixon for the book and says she has not been well and will not be celebrating Christmas; sends greetings to Mrs. Nixon and her family.
  - Grace King to Mrs. Nixon Monday, ALS, 2p.
    Invites Mrs. Nixon for tomorrow and hopes that Mrs. Warner will play because she is a delightful musician.
  - Grace King to Julia Ward Howe Monday, ALS, 2p.
    Invites Mrs. Howe to hear Mrs. Warner play tomorrow afternoon.
  - Grace King to Mrs. Nixon Saturday, ALS, 2p.
    Reminds Mrs. Nixon that she promised to have lunch with her today; tells her that Mrs. Hopkinson Smith will be there.
  - Magazine print of Grace King n.d., Print.